tell me y'all seen that meme that's like two days after a breakup a woman already got twenty
thousand dollars in her savings account five degrees a down payment on the house a mercedes
ben c class like her life just skyrockets right after a breakup from a toxic person
yeah yeah you know what i'm talking about so i know why that is it's because all the time that
you spend in mental confusion and emotional disarray trying to figure out why this toxic
person isn't treating you right and doesn't see your value when you see theirs and they're not
reciprocating the energy and love that you give to them and it's just mental chaos all over the place
you're spending so much time and energy in this shit show of a relationship that you can't even
focus on your passion and purpose because you're putting so much of your energy here so when you
finally cut off that energy now you can actually put it into the shit you're supposed to be paying
attention to and that's why life goes on baby